

Maksim Svistukhin

DETAILS

n Prague, Czech Republic

+420 608594057

SKILLS

Excelent communication
Front-end development
Web design
Direct sales
Solution design

LANGUAGES

Team management

English C1
Czech C1
Russian NATIVE

TECH SKILLS

HTML CSS JavaScript
React Git
SCSS Sketch Adobe CS
Webflow Figma

PROFILE '

I am a strong professional in communication at all levels. I have an extensive experience in team management and sales, as well as decent skills in web design and SW development. Overall, I can describe myself as a person, passionate about finding solutions for a rather wide range of potential issues.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY -

Front-end developer

2/2020 - Current

Berlin, Germany

EdgeCase Technology

- · Creating quality mockups and prototypes in Figma
- · Web development using HTML, CSS and JavaScript(React)

Team manager

Prague Group Adventures s.r.o. 12/2017 - 2/2019

Prague, Czech Republic

- · Create roadmaps and evaluate project performance
- · Hire, coach, onboard and motivate team members
- · Maintain both service quality and relations with suppliers

Team-leader (Customer support) 6/2016 – 10/2017

XEROX o.s.

Prague, Czech Republic

- · Collaborating with other departments to ensure that they met customer needs
- Track customer complaints to help identify areas where improvements can be made
- · Training and managing a team of customer support representatives

Customer Support Advisor

11/2014 - 6/2016

XEROX o.s.

Prague, Czech Republic

- Identify and assess customers' needs to achieve satisfaction
- Meet personal/customer service team sales targets and call handling quotas
- Provide accurate, valid and complete information by using the right methods/tools

Travel agent/Coordinator 2/2014 – 2/2018

Pissup Europe

Prague, Czech Republic

- · Sell and coordinate tours and activities
- Train newcomers
- Handle travel issues, conflicts, complaints

Luxury Retail Sales Manager 5/2011 - 8/2012

Boutique Vittoria

Samara, Russia

- · Support consultants in closing sales
- Set individual sales plans and KPI
- Remain aware of industry trends, to determine strategic opportunities to maximize sales within the market

EDUCATION -

Operations management, bc

Samara State Technical University Samara, Russia

Management, bc

Czech University of Life Sciences Prague